With great power comes great pain
The Unhealer is a fantasy, thriller, horror film directed by Martin Guigui.
A botched faith healing bestows supernatural
Shaman powers on a bullied teenager.
When his lifelong tormentors pull a prank that kills someone he loves, he uses his
powers for revenge and goes on a bloody rampage to settle the score.
Bernice, played by Natasha Henstridge.
Pflueger, played by Lance Henriksen.
Sheriff Adler, played by Adam Beach.
Gus, played by Chris Browning.
Red Elk, played by Branscombe Richmond.
Sarah, played by Angeline Appel.
The Unhealer is an American supernatural horror film written by Kevin E.
Moore and J.
Shawn Harris, directed by Martin Guigui, and
produced by siblings Cristi Harris and J.
Shawn Harris along with Tony Hannagan and Galen Walker.
It stars Lance Henriksen, Natasha Henstridge, Adam Beach, Elijah Nelson, Branscombe Richmond, Chris
Browning, Kayla Carlson, Angeline Appel, David Gridley, Will Ropp and Gavin Casalegno.
The film follows a bullied teenager who gains supernatural powers from a botched faith-healing then goes on
a revenge spree after a high school assault by his tormentors results in the unthinkable.
The Unhealer had its world premiere at Grimmfest film
festival, Manchester, England on October 9, 2020.
After a festival run, it was officially released on DVD,
Blu-ray, and streaming platforms on June 8, 2021.
The tone is dark and intense.